Mohawk Airlines Records
Mohawk Airlines Records
- Legal files
  - 14421
    - Allegheny Airlines Application for change in service pattern, non-stop Baltimore-EWR, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14394
    - Allegheny Application to allow non-stop all cargo Scranton/Wilkes Barre, Pa. and Cleveland, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14381
    - Allegheny Airlines Application to Alter point of origination or termination re: flights serving PVD-New York City-EWR, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14353
    - Allegheny Applications to serve non-stop between DCA-Hartford/Springfield, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14923
    - Application of Mohawk for amendment of certificate to serve Albany-HPN-DCA, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14827
    - Application of Mohawk to extend permission granted in 11495 re: HPN-DCA and intermediate points, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14811
    - Application of Mohawk to continue temporary suspension of service at Poughkeepsie, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14720
    - Application of Mohawk for transportation between Saranac/Lake Placid/Utica, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14271
    - Application for amendment of certificate Jamestown, N.Y., 1963 (Box 22)
  - 15015
    - Allegheny Airlines Application for exemption to overfly a segment junction point on certified flights between Cleveland and Atlantic City, N.Y., 1964 (Box 22)
  - 14895
    - Allegheny Airlines Application to amend its certificate to add new segment between terminal point Providence, R.I./terminal point Detroit, 1964 (Box 22)
  - 14983
    - Allegheny Application to amend certificate to serve Providence, Scranton, Wilkes-Barre, P.A., Cleveland, and Detroit, 1964 (Box 22)
  - 14976
    - Allegheny Airlines Application to amend certificate to re: segment #8 by adding HPN as an intermediate point, 1964 (Box 22)
  - 15760
    - Statewide Application for certificate to serve New York City/EWR-Hartford/Springfield, 1964 (Box 22)
  - 15734
    - City of HPN Application for certificate to provide service between HPN and Albany, 1964 (Box 22)
  - 15733
    - Statewide Application for exemption to operate aircraft in excess of 12,500 lbs, 1964 (Box 22)
  - 15560
    - State of New Hampshire, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 15457
    - Trans New England Application to serve Montreal, Canada/Burlington, Vermont and points mentioned in 15456, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 15456
    - Trans New England Application to serve over a new route states of Maine, Connecticut, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, New York, Rhode Island, and Vermont, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 15426
    - North Central Application to serve Chicago/ Toronto, Cleveland/Toronto, Milwaukee/Toronto, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 15494
    - Application of Mohawk for amendment to terminate Olean from segment 5 thus serve Cleveland/Boston with intermediate points, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 15237
    - Application of Mohawk to fly between Boston/Toronto, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 15167
    - Application of Mohawk to allow flights between Buffalo/Springfield/Westfield, Massachusetts, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 15090
    - Application of Mohawk to delete Poughkeepsie, 1964; 3 foldes (Box 23)
  - 14982
    - Application of Mohawk to authorize non-stop service between Buffalo and Detroit, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 14981
    - Application of Mohawk to authorize non-stop service between Providence and Detroit, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 14980
    - Application of Mohawk to add Detroit as terminal point to segment 3 of route 94, 1964 (Box 23)
  - 16693
    - Allegheny Airlines Application to extend segment 8 beyond Islip, L.I. to HPN and Albany, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 15956
    - Allegheny Airlines for Amendment of its certificate re: route 97, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 15496
    - Allegheny Airlines Application for removal of its certificate for segment #8, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16699
    - New Castle Application for amended certificate of Piedmont Aviation, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16698
    - New Castle Application for amended certificate for Lake Central, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16697
    - New Castle Application for amended certificate for Mohawk Airlines, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16676
    - Bridgeport Application for service Bridgeport/Buffalo with interpoints, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16456
    - Piedmont Application for amendment of certificate for Route 87, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16418
    - Orange County Airport for amendment to Mohawk's certificate to add Montgomery to Route 94, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16133
    - Statewide Application for Certificate to serve co-terminals in NYC/HPN/EWR and 35 points in New England, N.Y., Pa., and DCA, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16015
    - Town of Islip Application for service L.I. Airport, Albany, Syracuse, Rochester, and Buffalo, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 15924
    - Massachusetts Helicopter Application for certificate of Public Convenience, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16453
    - Application of Mohawk for amendment to serve Syracuse, Utica, Binghamton, Elmira, Philadelphia, and DCA, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16439
    - Application of Mohawk to provide service between terminal points Islip, L.I. and Detroit, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 16172
    - Application of Mohawk to overfly ERI on segment 6 of Route 94 on flights utilizing BAC-1-11 equipment, 1965 (Box 23)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk to overfly ERI on segment 7 on Route 94 utilizing One Eleven Equipment (never filed), 1965 (Box 23)
  - 15866
    - Mohawk Application to serve DTT and YYZ, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 15863
    - Application of Mohawk to serve Buffalo/Montreal via Rochester, 1965 (Box 23)
  - 17812
    - Allegheny Airlines for amendment of its certificate re: segment 5 of route 97, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17575
    - Allegheny Airlines for amendment to provide service to Chicage via Midway Airport, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17079
    - Allegheny Airlines Application for all Cargo service between Cleveland/Philadelphia, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17861
    - Trans World Airlines Application for amendment of its certificate for route 2, to delete Allentown, Bethlehem, Easton, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17810, 17811
    - Allentown/Bethlehem/Easton Petition for issuance of Show Cause order, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17783
    - Newcastle Application for amendment of certificate of Allegheny, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17726
    - In the matter of the Gulf States Midwest Points Service Investigation, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17723
    - Lake Central Application to serve Chicago and Motion to Consolidate, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17716
    - Starflite Application for temporary exemption to provide DC-3 Charter Service between NYC and 450 mile radius, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17699
    - Lake Central Application for amendment re: route 88 and Conditional Motion to Consolidate, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17574
    - Starflite Application to operate between LGA and Balston Spa, N.Y., 1966 (Box 23)
  - [??]
    - Eastern Airlines Application for License to operate International scheduled service into and from Canada, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 16828
    - Lake Central Application to Serve DTT-YYZ, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 15632
    - Starflite Application for renewal of authority to operate between New York City and East Hampton, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17809
    - Mohawk Application to provide service Rochester/Jamestown/Bradford/Pittsburg and for amendment of segment 5 deleting Jamestown/Olean, 1966 (Box 23)
  - [??]
    - Mohawk Application to non-stop service Buffalo/JFK and Rochester/JFK, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17704
    - Mohawk Application to serve terminal points Erie, Pa. and Chicago, Ill. via Midway Airport, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17649
    - Mohawk Application for authorization to serve both Olean and Jamestown on flights to New York City, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17207
    - Mohawk Application for amendment to serve between Rochester/YYZ and Buffalo/YYZ, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 17208
    - Mohawk to serve non-stop between Rochester/Toronto Application, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 7142, Buffalo/Toronto Case
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Book 3, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Book 4, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - 12837, United Competitive Examination
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Book 3, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - 8008, General Passenger Fare Examination
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Book 4, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Book 3, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Book 5 (Box 25)
  - 9181, Erie/Detroit Case
    - 1st Case (Box 25)
  - 6436, North Eastern Area Investigation
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Book 3, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Book 4, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 6927, Erie/Detroit Case
    - 2nd Case (Box 26)
  - 6125, Niagara Falls Airport Case
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 4251, Great Lakes Local Service Investigation
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Book 3, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - 7263, Pittsburgh/Syracuse
    - [Miscellaneous], 2 folders (Box 27)
  - 13166, Ogdensburg Temporary Suspension Investigation
    - [Miscellaneous] (Box 27)
  - 10161, Temporary Intermediate Points
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Book 2 (Box 27)
  - 8569, New York Airways Certificate Renewal
    - Book 1 (Box 27)
    - Book 2 (Box 27)
    - Book 3 (Box 28)
  - 10917, Passenger Credit Plan Investigation
    - [Miscellaneous], 2 folders (Box 28)
  - 1335, Service to Ogdensburg Investigation
    - Book 1 (Box 28)
    - Book 2 (Box 28)
  - 12130, Eastern-Mohawk Route Transfer
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - 9973, New York Air Cargo Investigation
    - Book 1, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Book 3, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - 8404, Rate of Return Local Service Carriers
    - Book 1 (Box 29)
    - Book 2, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Book 3, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Book 4, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Book 5, 2 folders (Box 30)
- Publicity
  - Newspaper clippings
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 31)
    - General, 1957; 5 volumes (Box 32)
    - General, 1957; 4 volumes (Box 33)
    - General, 1958; 2 volumes (Box 33)
    - Sampson Air Force Base publicity, 1955-1957 (Box 33)
  - News releases, 1955-1959; 4 volumes (Box 34)
  - News releases, 1960-1961; 2 volumes (Box 35)
  - Newsletters, 1954-1961; 2 volumes (Box 35)
  - Advertising tear sheets (Box 35)
  - Information bulletins, circa 1964-1966; 2 volumes (Box 35)
  - Supervisors' newsletters, 1958-1960; 2 volumes (Box 36)
- Statistical files
  - Passenger load, 1956-1957 (Box 36)
  - Passenger load, 1957-1958 (Box 37)
  - Passenger load, 1958-1959 (Box 38)
  - Operating, Ray and Ray, 1953 (Box 38)
  - Operating, Ray and Ray, 1954-1957 (Box 39)
  - Operating, Ray and Ray, 1959; 1961 (Box 40)
  - Airline operating statistics, 1949-1950 (Box 40)
  - Comparative operating statistics, 1952 (Box 41)
  - Interline (Box 41)
  - Local service (Box 41)
  - Airport activity atatistics, Mar 1963; Jun 1964; 2 folders (Box 41)
- Financial files
  - Statements
    - Unbound, 1959-1961; 1963-1964,; 1967 (Box 42)
    - Bound, 1956; 1959 (Box 42)
    - Bound, 1960-1962 (Box 43)
  - Operating forecasts, 1956-1960 (Box 43)
- Bound reports
  - Segment Load, 1954; 1958-1959,; 1964 (Box 43)
  - General Schedules
    - General Schedule 1-10, Extra Section Schedule 1 through 3 (Box 44)
    - General Schedule 11-17 (Box 44)
    - General Schedule #3 (Box 44)
    - General Schedule #24 (Box 44)
  - Quick Reference Schedules (master copy) (Box 44)
  - Mohawk Station Analysis (Box 44)
  - Mohawk Station Traffic (Box 44)
  - Mohawk Traffic Manual (Box 45)
  - Traffic Flow Analysis (unduplicated) (Box 45)
  - Traffic Flow Analysis (duplicated) (Box 45)
  - System Timetable (Box 45)
  - Diagramatic Ship Routing (Box 45)
  - Engineering Survey (Box 45)
  - Convair Operation Report (Box 45)
  - Transfers, Q-U (Box 46)
  - Traffic, H-J (Box 46)
- General files
  - Financial forecasts, 1956-1966 (Box 47)
  - Marketing Department
    - Advertising (Box 47)
    - Equipment Change, 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Program (Box 47)
    - Public Relations (Box 47)
    - Research Project (Box 47)
    - Reservation Center, 3 booklets (Box 47)
    - Publications (Box 47)
    - Robinson Airlines, 6 folders (Box 47)
    - Smithsonian (Box 47)
    - R.V. Stephenson (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous
  - Books, 10 volumes (Box 47)
  - Books (Box 48)
  - Film (Box 48)
  - General Schedule Transmittals (Box 48)
  - Ship Routing Statistical Data (Box 48)
  - Helicopter Airlines, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box 48)
  - Local Service Airlines, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box 48)